Anping Bridge is also called Wuli Bridge.
It is the longest existing cross-sea beam stone bridge in China.
There is a saying that no bridge in the world is longer than this.
Walk across Wuli Bridge,
and you'll be safe and worry-free.
Excuse me,
what is a cross-sea beam stone bridge?
It is a bridge that crosses an ocean or a bay.
Wang Jun.
What about its main structure?
You have eyes, don't you?
There was an introduction just now.
If you still don't understand,
just look it up online.
I just wanted specific details.
Leave.
Don't waste my time.
Why are you all standing around?
I paid for it.
A cross-sea stone bridge
is mainly composed of stone piers
and stone beams placed on them.
Thank you.
Connecting fate across the sea,
stable for a thousand years.
There is a saying here:
as long as couples walk across this bridge hand in hand,
they will share one heart,
and grow old together.
I know, but we
have basic costs.
But that quote is really low.
Feifei.
I think
if that's the case...
I'll try to find a way to add some manpower for you.
What?
I held it last time.
It's your turn this time.
Still you this time.
No, you hold it.
Hold it.
You hold it.
Go.
Then does it count as holding hands while crossing the bridge?
That's not the point.
The point is today's guests are so weird.
If you think traveling is a waste of time,
you should wait until you have time.
Don't worry.
To deal with weird guests like this,
I have my own ways.
See what you two would like to eat.
Ginger duck and oyster omelette
are the signature dishes here
and our local specialties.
Feifei,
tell me if you're not satisfied.
They didn't do anything wrong.
Don't you think it's a waste of money?
It's not expensive.
Before we came,
they both told me.
Spending 1,000 on a normal graphics card
and spending 20,000 on a top-tier one.
Which one would you choose?
I'd buy the 1,000 one first.
When I save enough money,
I'll upgrade to a better one.
If you have to spend that money eventually,
why not choose the best one from the start?
Since I gave you full authority to buy the graphics card,
you should have
made the best choice from the start,
instead of bringing a normal one home.
Understood?
What does that mean?
Go.
What does this have to do with graphics cards?
It's an analogy.
Comparing cheap restaurants to ordinary graphics cards,
and taking a jab at Zhang Yang.
And Li Xinyue.
It's not your fault the client is complaining.
If they really valued quality,
they should have booked a high-end tour with another big agency,
instead of choosing us.
Are we not high-end?
But we offer great value for money.
But it's so strange.
Traveling with someone you like
is supposed to be a happy thing.
Why seize every chance to lose their temper?
You even used 'seize every chance'.
You have a sharp tongue.
Shut up.
Xinyue, go on.
Because it's a break-up trip.
Break-up trip?
Yes.
She has a
pretty bad temper.
So,
please don't mind her.
With all due respect...
How should I put it?
She is quite busy with work.
And most of my time
is spent taking care of her daily life.
So,
I don't have much income.
Occasionally,
I also help her with some work-related matters.
For this break-up trip,
the money we use
is all hers too.
So,
I
don't want to spend too much,
or it would make me look like a gold-digger
trying to make a fortune before breaking up.
It's weird
for me to say this, right?
You want the best conditions,
but preferably without spending a penny,
right?
She means
she understands you want this trip
to be extremely cost-effective.
It's okay.
These past few days
have been when she's had the best attitude.
Tell you what, sir.
We will go back
and plan a new route for you.
We'll call you to discuss it then,
okay?
Okay.
After Xing Fei was promoted to project manager,
she didn't have time to spend with Wang Jun,
so she broke up with him.
Xing Fei is from Nan'an.
When they first got together,
she told Wang Jun she wanted to visit Nan'an,
but she never had the time.
So he suggested this breakup trip.
So,
we must make sure he has no regrets.
But Xing Fei could have just refused this trip.
Does she still have feelings?
Who said that?
Fulfilling a promise doesn't mean she still has feelings.
But I agree with what you said.
They shouldn't be left with any regrets.
Agreed.
Are you hungry?
Not hungry.
Let me make you a midnight snack.
No, thanks.
Why?
I was afraid you'd ask me for a service fee.
Or maybe
you ordered cheap takeout
and asked me for a high kickback.
I won't charge you.
In your heart,
am I such a hateful person?
In the past,
I thought you were quite hateful when I disliked you.
I don't dislike you anymore.
You don't dislike me now?
I don't.
Why the sudden change of heart?
Are you okay?
It's hot.
Did you find the place?
I...
found it.
This is inappropriate.
What are you doing?
I'm sleepy.
Sleepy, huh?
How about now?
Are you still sleepy?
Not sleepy anymore.
Let's continue.
I might need some ice.
I can go get some ice.
You guys continue.
What else do you need? I'll go get it.
You guys.
Hurry up, hurry up.
Why are you three
acting so strange today?
Just tell me if you have something to say.
Mr. Zhang, did you put on perfume today?
Perfume? This is the smell of my laundry pods.
Mr. Zhang, aren't you cold wearing so little?
I'm naturally not afraid of the cold.
Mr. Zhang, your hairstyle looks very handsome today.
Haven't I always been this handsome?
Do you guys have something to say or not?
It's too red.
A little lighter.
Hello.
Okay, okay, okay.
I will check my email later for the offer letter.
Thank you.
I will think about it carefully. Thank you.
Of all times.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Today,
it's really cold.
I remember when I was in school,
I used to put my hands down my desk mate's neck,
and make him scream from the cold.
Let's turn on the AC.
Let's go.